Good, yeah,
doing Yeah,
a little bit. Uh,
yeah, I think we last spoke in February,
right? So, uh, it's a little bit of time.
Yeah, but it was very good progress in the meantime.
I'm very happy about it. I think I mentioned this. Sorry about my poor
cam today. I typically use an external webcam.
I seem to have forgotten it today,
so it doesn't get better than what you see.
Um,
yeah, great. What are your, if I may ask,
what are your plans for the, uh,
April getaway? Yeah,
so, uh, for April, I have a quick trip.
I'm gonna head over to Thailand, uh,
and, uh, yeah, just, like, meet up with some friends.
Kind of an impromptu trip, uh,
but, uh, yeah, it'll, I,
I don't imagine, honestly, we'll meet with, uh, uhm,
like, with airlines, and, and oil,
and the war, yeah, that I'll probably travel very much else,
like, for a while this year,
so I'm kind of just getting it out of the way now. Okay,
okay, well, yeah, great, wonderful. That's great.
Um, sounds good.
Yeah, I hope you will get there safely,
and, uh, back, um, without any, uh, any problems.
Absolutely, thank you so much. Uhm,
very high level, Vista,
I had, uh, still, you know, these contract negotiations,
I met the CEO last week,
and very high level, everything takes a little bit longer,
and it's a little more, you know, it takes an extra left and right
turn, but the good news is everything is still on track,
so there's still on board, uh, they agreed,
at least orally, on the, uhm,
65K contract that I've sent them initially in January,
and, uhm,
they, uhm,
yeah, there's another meeting with the CEO next week,
Thursday, but, uh,
that's more, like, you know, operational aspects,
but not nothing to be worried about, and,
uhm, the team is also still very committed to position
the tool with other science parks,
so, you know, everything that we,
we planned is, is on, on, on track in terms of,
it's still on the plan, and, uh, they are committed,
so that's very good, uhm, even if things take a little bit longer,
but that's, uh, you know, somewhat normal, uhm,
I believe, and I'd, I'd like don't mind it so much,
although I believe it's important to pick up in speed before,
before it's irrelevant, and I guess the, the highest,
uh, the most important thing that, uh, is a little bit shocking on the
one hand, uhm,
is also linked to, you know, the speed that,
that we showed so far, that,
uh, just due to, you know, overall geopolitical,
uh, developments, this kind whole sustainability aspect is,
at least when you sell things,
uh, more difficult to sell now than,
uhm, than, uh,
you know, six months or one year ago.
And I remember when I spoke with the CEO,
uh, last time, he said, oh yeah, no, Vista continues to be committed to
sustainability, and so, you know, everything's fine.
And now he said, uh, well, he loves, still loves the topic.
But he has to sell it to his, like, uh,
you know, whatever board, and,
uh, so now they say if we position it more as a general,
uh, portfolio management tool, then it will be easier.
And, uhm,
and that's possible given the news cases that we,
sorry, the use cases that we added, like the news feature,
uh, the AI agent, that makes it accessible for different,
uh, uhm, management positions within Vista,
and, you know, initially, I only targeted this as a sustainability,
uh, thing, and based on the feedback,
we've, you know, added these, uh, functions already,
so, uhm,
yeah, so that's still, you know, a little bit of an iteration that we
need to do, also, how do we position it with other,
uh, science parks, do we still position it as the systemic impact thing,
I would love to do it, or do we need to position it more
as a collaboration and growth, uh,
tool, uhm, so that's very high-level,
and, uh, one thing that we'll be looking into next week is
with someone who is, who has taken over a new,
uh, building with five floors,
and, uh, they are,
uhm, they are, they have a lot of,
uh, government funding and support to set up,
uh, like, uhm,
games, uhm,
hub, uh, with some of the large players,
uh, in, you know, the games development,
but also smaller players, and they need to,
they need to fill up their space, and also some,
uh, changes that Berlin now has more difficulties filling up their space.
Their, uh, their, uh, real estate,
so, you know, demand is going down a little bit,
so now they're more worried about how can we fill up the space,
and, uhm, so I met with that person,
uh, a few days ago,
and, uhm, the question is,
I, I showed them the tools and said, well, sustainability is actually,
even in our field is also relevant,
there's like a sustainable board,
For.gov and, you know, some educational games,
and we could position this as, like, a value-added,
so, you know, he said it's completely fine.
Uh, one thing that he potentially would,
uh, be interested in, and where at first thought we could deliver it,
and now I'm a little more hesitant, is,
uh, some, uhm,
leads identification, where basically,
uh, he would, uh, give us,
or us, our, uh, software,
uh, sample companies with some,
uh, uhm, criteria that he's looking for,
let's say, you know, uh, games,
uh, or organizations,
uh, active in the game sector, uh,
you know, maximum size in terms of employees,
are there any growth indicators that show,
you know, recent hiring, or recent funding?
Thanks. Uh, to make sure that, you know, they get some growth companies rather
than those, you know, who, who stay constant or are declining,
and, uh, then he, you know, he'd say these are some of the companies
that I, I know that are relevant, and then could we come up with,
uh, companies that,
uh, are similar, uh, potentially in different geographic regions,
so that would almost be like a lead, uh, generation tool.
and and, uhm,
I said, you know, we can discuss the requirements,
what sort of companies is he interested in,
which databases would we need to tap into,
and, uh, you know, how sophisticated should it be,
and that's, you know, one thing we,
we can see to what degree we can add it as a,
as a tool, uhm,
and we can discuss next week. Uh,
and, uhm, alright.
And then, I guess, given the fact that,
you know, I realized in general already we need to,
to increase our speed, uhm,
you know, once the contract is signed,
uhm, and payments come in,
uhm,
I still believe, you know, we can push you to more or less a
full-time, whether it's by a full-time payment or in the incentive payments,
uhm, so that's still, you know,
in, in, in the making. I believe even, uh,
I think 10k should come in, uh, fairly soon in the next,
uh, week or 10 days. So that,
you know, we could maybe add some incentive payments still for,
uh, for March. That could bring you to more or less a full-time,
uhm, position. Uhm,
but in the meantime, one comes relevant is that,
you know, we can, we, we have a good product and we want to,
A, give, uh, Vista, uhm,
access to, to use it and,
uh, potentially also other, uhm,
uh, new clients, potential clients and existing clients.
And what we need is sort of merge some of the functionalities that we
have in the old app with the new ones.
and There, I have a few questions,
uh, and I think we need to probably look into,
you know, I shared the video with you. Did you have the time to
look at the video? Yeah. Yeah. No, not yet. Yeah. Yeah. I guess. Yeah.
Yeah. I guess the,
the best, uhm,
way to proceed, but you can correct me as maybe,
you know, just, uh, item by item.
So basically log in, how would that look like?
Uh, and then, uh, team management,
how would that look like? So then it's, you know, less complex,
but very high level. Um,
you know, we can either implement this as without
generic design, as we currently have with Impact Foresight,
which means, you know, we have a login screen and then you can create
your account or manage your account.
Um, but then, then we also have these Vista-specific,
um, uh,
login pages where we have the design with,
you know, uh, instead of the Impact Foresight,
um, uh, designs,
we have it with the Vista designs. Uh,
I can, you do remember which ones these are?
Like the login screen? Uh, it's not so much.
Um,
and, so,
yes, exactly. Okay. These are in Figma.
I can share them with you. Uh, I'll open them whilst we speak,
although it always takes so much, um, bandwidth that sometimes that slows everything down,
but let's just open this quickly.
Uh, Vista and Design,
Figma. Here we go. It takes a little while.
Um,
and my question is
very high level. Do you know how we would do it if,
you know, the idea is that we generate for Vista a white label solution
where the login does not happen on, uh,
uhm, impact for a site,
but happens on, uh, you know,
a subdomain at, uh,
at, at Vista? Bye for now. And then obviously there's the technical implementation
that, you know, they log in at,
uh, maybe app.vista.de or whatever.
But then there's also the design aspect. how does our
app know when to show the Vista-specific design versus
when to show the generic impact
foresight design or maybe some other customer's design.
Is that simply by telling it as soon as someone logs in at,
for example, app.vista.de,
then this automatically leads, like, to the Vista-specific design?
Is that how it works? Or, uh, uh,
how would, uh, how would we know, you know, which design do we show
the user? Uhm,
yeah, it, There's a couple of different ways that it can work
that have, uh, a lot of various levels of complexity,
to be perfectly honest. Uhm,
there's one way where, for example,
they would have to install,
like, basically add, like, what you might think of as,
like, a URL forwarder. and I'll see time.
Uh, like when it goes to,
um, a certain link,
it would forward to our app and then our app,
um, would pick up that traffic and show,
like, like Vista. Um,
and then, but like, uh,
one way we can do that is actually by having a,
uh, like Vista specific version of our app.
Um,
so that, so that means that we would have two apps basically,
but I think that it could be worth it if you want everything to
be, like, white-labeled different.
Um, I mean, that's one way to do it.
There's a couple other ways. I, I think, I think we were scoping this
out before. Um,
so I'm trying to look into that, but, uh.
Yeah. Yeah. I mean, I mean, it does, it, it, it does take some,
like, depending on how deeply you want the white-label,
um, then it increases the complexity.
Okay. So, it's, it's definitely possible, but it's,
it's just a trade-off of how much, um,
how much white-label versus, like, time. Sure.
Um, I think the reason why I'm bringing it up now is that,
you know, initially in the video that I shared with you, I said,
Let's just add the footer. Functionality is from the old app into the new
app. And now that,
uh, you know, Vista, um,
makes, uh, the payments and we realize time is important,
I thought, okay, maybe instead of, uh, you know,
doing everything in the old app, why not already,
you know, implement directly the Vista designs so,
uh, you know, we can test it with them.
And if I use it then with other clients,
I can tell them. and well, that's currently, you know, Vista-specific design and,
uh, you'll obviously get your own design or,
or, you know, uh, if you want a white-label solution,
uhm, so, you know,
we have to, and the Vista designs are a little bit different to
our, you know, old, uhm,
designs, but that concerns primarily the login screens,
which is, you know, not many pages, uh, just,
uh, You know, it's blue for Impact Foresight here,
it's, and there's, like, the Vista logo and a bit of Vista design,
uhm, for the login screens,
and, uhm, the second part that's a little bit different,
let me just show this to you, is,
uhm, just move this around,
so here, if we look in, uh,
the, uhm, profile of,
uhm,
your, uh,
Vista company dashboard,
that would be, like, a, you know, a venture that has logged in,
that wants to manage their, their impact, currently we,
all we have is here, we still have these same things,
Edit Venture Profile, My Portfolios, My Ventures,
Manage Team, and Logout, Thank you.
But then, the, we just have,
you know, when they log in, Manage Public Profile,
you know, there's less, less, functionalities available,
let's say, this way, so probably we need to look into detail,
you know, on, on the different, uhm,
Manage Public Profile, I mean,
I need to look into it, because I like to the simplicity of the
designs here, you know, if our old app has so many functionalities and then
gets complex, I thought, oh, you know, it would, would just be nice,
you know, you can log in, then you manage your profile,
obviously, uh,
Edit Venture Profile, well,
at this point in time, they can't,
ah, you know, they can edit their Venture Profile, they edit the Public Profile,
they would call it. Mhm. Mhm. Mm-hmm.
My Portfolios, this would probably be only be relevant for,
uhm,
the questions, would we want, ah, you know, each company,
ah, to, ah, to create a Portfolio,
we need to think about it, but I wouldn't mind it,
or we could also say for a Venture, you know,
only Portfolio Managers get access to this one here to make it less complex,
we need to decide, uhm,
you know, and then my Ventures there
would see the, yeah, Manage Team.
So basically, if I look at it now, sorry for the little bit back
and forth. It's okay. Yeah,
I, I think we should look at the old app and see the functionalities
that we have there, and then discuss how can we add them to
the new app, and I still believe, please correct me if you believe that's,
uh, we have a different view.
Based on what we've done so far, it makes sense to just use the
code from the old app and add it to our new app,
and at some point in time, I think the old app will be phased
out, and we just reuse what we can and,
uh, rebuild everything.
I believe, you know, using the old and the new one is complex,
and, uh, so we just reuse the code whenever we can.
Does that make sense, uh, in your opinion, to reuse the code and especially
the different, uh, you know, use cases now,
the Edit My Profile,
uh, maybe even Manage Team,
Edit My Ventures, and we can just reuse what we have in the old
app. I know that in some cases we need to,
you know, adapt, where do we get the data from and so on,
but it might I hope is that it will still be quicker than,
you know, if you had to do everything from scratch. Mhm,
uhm,
yeah, uhm, yeah, I think it, I'm trying to think.
So the old app is, is,
uh, it's pretty large, I would say,
and then we have the new app, and then,
And are you saying all of like,
like, would you, and then you're saying,
uh, you'd ideally want to reuse as much code as possible from the old
app and the new app, right? Uhm,
no, I don't care. I don't care whether we reuse the code,
but I think we can use a lot of the functionality that we have
in the old app can be reused in the new app.
I believe your designs are a little bit superior.
I don't like some of the designs in the old app,
but they're pretty functional and the,
they, you know, the whole way to either manage a company or manage
a portfolio, add a team member,
sharing access. And so it's pretty sophisticated and works well.
So I, you know, we can reuse this and maybe make the design
more beautiful later. Uhm, or you'd say right away,
oh, I don't want to use old code. It's, it's so different now because
our data sources are not the same and,
you know, we need to rebuild everything. Then you can, you know,
just, uh, build it new.
But in terms of the functionalities, what we have in the old app needs
to be in the new app because basically we need to be able to
log into the old app, into the new app. We need to be able
to edit your profile. we need to be able to create
a portfolio. My vision is that a portfolio manager can create many,
several portfolios. And all of this,
you know, the, the dashboard and the UI and,
and obviously the backend also exists in the old app.
So I would just say, well, we can reuse this. Um,
the problem is currently, it's, you know, either the old or the new app,
and that's not very, uh, user-friendly.
Yeah, for sure. And we can, you know,
we can, we can take it step by step.
So very specifically, if I just see if I can close this,
if I go to the old app and, uhm, obviously we have something that
we do not have in the,
uh,
new app. We have this top header here.
With the top right, uhm,
uh, menu, I find this header,
it takes a lot of space. I would almost prefer if we did not
have the header, we could almost, you know, use everything that we have here
and put it as it is in our, let me just go to the
new app. Let's go to my portfolios,
let's just use this one here.
Camp Neural Database,
well, actually, yeah, there would,
let's go to the dashboard here,
you know. I'm not sure whether we need,
you know, this, this top bar,
uh, as, as we have it,
uhm, in the end. The old app, it would,
you know, potentially take more space, or whether we,
yeah, and then just add the functionality,
uh, you know, on the left, or we say we don't use,
like, the logo. Let me just go, if we go to,
you know, there's also, how do you call this, uh, breadcr,
uh, no, that's a new app, oops, sorry, uh,
where's, how can I go to the old one?
I believe, you know, if I click on, uh,
if I click on My Portfolios,
you know, you see this, uh, this, how do you call it,
breadcrumb thing? Yeah. Yeah,
I mean, that's somewhat useful, so,
you know, that's one decision we need to take. Do we want to show
this? Do we want to, you know,
add it to all screens in the new app,
or, uh, You know, I'm not entirely sure.
You know, you can think about, uh,
about it. However, now, looking at the functionalities,
and also what I find somewhat helpful, sorry,
is if I log in, you know, if I, if I,
I'm at my profile, I see Ingo Miklfeuler.
If I go to My Portfolios and I select a portfolio,
then I see, ah, okay, it's Haitian Women's Collective.
If code too. If to My Ventures and I select a venture,
then I always see which,
ah, venture I'm editing. We don't know
this. We don't need the certification process here.
Uhm, so,
yeah, but I'm not sure how,
how to do it. I'm undecided. But what we certainly need as a first
step is after login,
edit my profile. And,
uh, that's not beautiful, but, yeah,
but still, it's, it's functional. You know, it allows me to edit my profile
and it allows me to, uh, deactivate my account and change my password.
I would say, you know, from my perspective, we can just reuse this.
The second aspect is that, uh, subscription on the old app
is, uh, is on a venture level. Basically, if I add a new venture,
if, you know, my account needs a subscription and if I don't have a
subscription, it will ask me, you know,
please, uh, create a subscription.
So, this is something that we don't necessarily need
for Vista, but we needed for other clients and at some point
in time I think we can, uh,
you know, reuse this and add it also to the new app.
Do we need it right now? Probably not.
But basically, you know, if I go to, I'm still in the old app
and if I now go to, just go to my ventures and I say
add a new venture, then it will probably ask me to create a new
subscription, a new venture. Uh,
oh, exactly. And then I, you know, I need to purchase a new subscription.
If I have one open, then, uh, it will allow me to, uh, to,
uh, This,
I don't think we need to add directly to the new app.
So, we could say initially, well, let's just copy the code for my profile.
And, you know, that's a simple, uhm,
thing where after login, I can edit my profile and can we,
you know, just copy this code and add it to our new app.
The benefit is that then finally they can log in in directly into their
app and don't always need to go into the old app first.
Right, right. So, like, after login,
they should land on the new app. And then there should be a way
to click for my profile and see a page like this.
Yes, however, yeah,
however, I still have clients using the old app,
so I, if they now,
you know, go to the new app, we have a problem.
So I'm not sure whether we need to call it instead of app impact
for studio Call it Vista or
ImpactForesight.io or,
uh, we set it up directly as we can't set up a subdomain for,
for Vista. Can we, they need to do it for us, correct?
Um,
I mean, we could say like Vista.ImpactForesight.io on our
end. I think we would have to change something,
uh, for our, for like GoDaddy DNS,
but I can update that. Um,
or, or like on a virtual machine, but yeah, I can look into that.
Um, I can also just make it such that,
like, any Vista email gets sent to the new app after login,
and like, I keep the old, I keep everyone else on the old app,
but then they specifically have a login page that's to the new app.
Um, so that's one way to do it.
Yeah. There's like a couple, I think there's a couple ways to do that,
actually. Okay.
Because there could be use cases where,
you know, if I want to show it to the demo to new clients
that are not necessarily Vista, probably it makes sense to give them also
access to the new app. Yeah. So,
uh,
maybe we could just call it.
Instead of app,
call it, uh, how could we, yeah, I'm
not entirely sure.
I, we need to think about it. That's open. Yeah.
That's, we can take that with us, but I think several solutions are possible
that are not hugely complex and very,
maybe slightly in terms of, you know, where do you need to go in
order to log in? Uh, because obviously if I all send them to the
app.impactprocessor.io login, then they would probably, you know, go to the old app and
maybe I need either a
Vista specific login page or
a, uh,
white label login page, uhm, that would lead to, uh, to the new app.
Yeah. Initially,
I think keeping it simple, I think it would be acceptable
to show the demo to new users with the Vista design.
Uh, it just, you know, it shows we have a customer,
it shows we are able to adapt our designs,
white label designs, so I would say,
uh, we could say, uhm,
you know, call it vista.impactprocessor.io And,
uh, this would be,
once you log into this page,
then obviously you're in the Vista design and,
uh, the Vista white label solution,
more or less. Mmm.
Okay. Okay. So,
uhm. That's maybe the best solution.
I like this because we want to proceed quickly with Vista.
And, uh, let's not care too much about, uh, a
white label or old app design and rather make it,
you know, make it work for Vista. So basically until we,
they create their own subdomain, uh,
like, uh, app.vista.de.
Yeah. Let's just create a white label solution on our servers and our subdomain.
just add a subdomain, uh, vista.impactforsat.io.
And then when you click on it, you would get to these, uh,
login pages. Oop, where do we have
them? And basically
the, the only way to log into our new app is, you know, using
the Vista designs. That's fine.
If we keep in mind that, have a neutral
design also, or, um,
or another white label customer. So I'm not sure,
you know, that will come at some point in time,
but initially for me, it's fine to say,
uh, you know, once you log into, uh,
uh, this specific,
uh, um,
subdomain on Impact Foresight, then you just go to the,
come to the new Vista design. Okay. and just to show you,
if I, if I, um,
these are exactly the same designs then, uh,
then we have in the, um, um,
old app, uh, it's just like the Vista design is different,
but the steps and the screens are the same. So basically if I log
out, just log out here, you see the same screens.
If I log in, uh,
you know, it's the same screen and just, you Here we have the Vista
design, and, uhm, if you look here,
you'd have the login. Yeah,
it's all the same, just the logo on the top and the Vista design,
it's, uh, it's slightly different. But, uh, the screens are,
are very, very similar, so I think we can probably reuse some of the
code, I assume. Mhm,
mhm,
Uhm, if I log in, Now, I don't need to create an account,
so probably that brings me directly to,
uh, you know, the login, but typically if I, you know, if I were
to create an account, I would go to the, through the same screens,
uh, just with, uh, a different,
uh, you know, the, the Impact Foresight,
uh,
color, uh, but very similar. Mhm,
mkay. Bye-bye. Yeah,
so that would be the login. And then the question is,
where do we position it? Do we position it on the top right?
Or do we position it at the left?
I'm not so sure. What is your first thought?
Uhm,
Maybe top right is good. We could probably do, like, bottom left or something.
I mean, we could put it anywhere,
to be honest. But, uhm,
yeah, maybe, like, bottom left, like a profile circle or something.
Or we could put it, like, top right as well.
I could try to see how both look, but that's,
Okay. Where to put this is,
like, one of the easier aspects of this session.
Great. Sounds good. Yeah. So,
then, uhm,
let's say we would, unless you have a different suggestion,
I'm very open, why not create a new subdomain,
vista.impactforset.io. And when you log in,
then we would implement, uh, these,
uh, login screens and,
uhm,
then And one question is, do we need to know whether we have someone
who is a Portfolio Manager? Like, would the screen,
the whole dashboard look differently if you're a Venture
versus, ah,
like a Portfolio Company versus the Portfolio Manager?
Uhm, I believe,
given that you gave me access, like, to extra drop-down menus in the as,
like, you know, the, uhm, admin tools,
my first suggestion would be, give,
ah, all whoever logs in the same functionality,
so basically a Vista Portfolio
Company would be able to create a Portfolio.
Uh, I think I would be willing to allow it to them,
maybe at some point in time we can charge them,
but, now the question is, if we realize that,
uh, you know, confuses them because they just say,
do I need to create a Portfolio, do I create a Venture,
what I need to do, is it possible to,
you know, on the individual basis say,
so typically, you know, a Portfolio does not show up unless we give,
uhm, uh,
a login, a user, like,
uh, Vista Dashboard, uh,
uh, functionalities, and then basically we would only have ten people in Vista,
uh, Portfolio access, but the default view would then be not
showing the Portfolios in the dropdown,
and only, you know, if you, if we grant them access.
Is that something that's possible, or? All right. Thank you.
Um, I think so. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, I'm sure. I'm not entirely sure.
Yeah. Spontaneously, I,
I'd love to use them, you know, if people find it helpful,
even companies, uhm,
why not allow them to create Portfolio, and if many do it,
uh, we can, you know, we charge them at some point in time.
So I would say initially let's just show,
you know, the same, uh, MediRoute,
and your items for anyone who logs in.
Okay. Uhm,
until I tell you to change it. Yeah. Okay, that sounds good.
Cool. Okay, so then we have the My Profile,
and there we said initially, as this will lead us only to the new
app, you could disregard the whole,
uhm, license,
uh, and billing, billing screen for,
uh, if you want to add a new venture.
Unless you say, oh, it's easier if I copy that right away,
then I'd love to have it.
But, uh, it's not, uhm,
uhm, uhm,
yeah, you know, if it takes time to add it, then I would say
let's add this maybe later. Yeah,
yeah, I'd have to look into it, but I, yeah,
I think,
I, I, I mean, I, I think it's always going to be faster if
we kind of take, like, step by step, right,
and we, like, verify, okay, this looks good, this looks good,
and, uhm, yeah, as opposed to doing,
like, a big, giant leap. Uh,
so maybe, we, we can maybe we leave it off for now,
and then, like, add it when we feel, like, everything else is settled,
and we just, like, we can add it in somehow, and then if I
have to deal with any issues doing that, then, it's,
like, isolated, uhm, as opposed to it kind of being,
like, this big, uh, you know, this big,
this big endeavor where it takes a long time to even get,
like, a first iteration, so. Yeah.
And book a mentor session, I would say,
if it doesn't, take a lot of time to, that's just,
uh, you know, opens a link, uhm,
I assume that's, shouldn't, you know, be complex to add,
I would say, Yeah, that's fine. Let's just keep it,
uh, maybe it confuses them because they reach out to ImpactForesight,
and they should rather reach out to, uh, Vista,
but, uh, you know, we can always, I assume,
hide or show this menu item.
You know,
easily, uh, and for the moment,
I should, why don't show it, it's good, it looks professional.
Okay. And then, and then,
we have the issue,
maybe, first would be,
My Ventures. And,
uhm,
so here we have a very different functionality. We have the old app,
where basically, if you click on a Venture,
you have this whole thing of, okay, we have the AI impact logic generation,
and, uh, theory of change overview,
uh,
but we also have, like, forecasting impact potential,
and so on. Uhm,
and this might change a lot, uh,
I think we'll use as, you know, the standard template,
our new AI generated, uh,
internal company profiles, and the only thing that we will need to give Vista
portfolio companies access to is managing
their public profile, and,
uhm, Cheers.
Maybe we could,
uh, because basically, Vista,
as a portfolio manager, has already access to all their companies in this database
view. Mhm. They don't need,
uh, this, uh,
MyVentures, it's like a duplication,
it's like a, uhm,
they don't need this. They already have access, uh,
you know, in the new app to the list of ventures. Okay.
So, basically, we could almost say,
uh,
yeah, we don't need this one here. For, if it's for Vista.
Okay. So we can just remove it. Remove the MyVentures aspect.
Yes. All right.
I mean, if, I mean, if it's possible,
so, um, and you know this,
but I'm just gonna repeat it again. Definitely one of the trickiest parts of
our app right now is, uh,
the two, like the fact that we have ventures.
And we have a lot of code that's built off of that,
uh, data concept. And then we have the extracted companies,
right. And then we have code in the new app that's built off of
like that concept. Right. And so, um,
trying to get anything to work across the two right now can be,
uh, can just take like more time.
Um, so. Yes. And I don't think it's necessary.
Yeah. So you'd, so, you know, uh,
yeah, if you're saying that we don't need the ventures in
the new app for now, and we don't need,
you know, what's dependent on that too, either,
then, you know, then that decreases some complexity.
Right. So. Yes, I think that's,
that's okay. Uh, that's okay.
We do have a few clients like, uh, like, um,
the Nadasa Dedo and,
um, the HWC and women's,
uh, Haitian Women's Collective who have built,
uh, you know, profiles of their ventures in the old
app and who I would also love to give access to the new app.
But, um, let's focus on Vista.
That's great. It's our biggest paying client at the moment and my assumption is
that, um,
everything that's in the new app, including like the detailed,
uh, measurement and theory of change and so on,
well, it was a little bit too complex anyways.
So I believe you know in the next step We will probably use our
AI agent that is able to maybe then edit different sustainability
concepts and then basically,
you know, in the next phase,
once we've implemented like the portfolio management tool,
then we say, okay, now we want to give,
uh, all, uhm,
uh, URL extracted companies the possibility
to edit some of their sustainability concepts.
So, basically, we'd say, let's start with, with, uh,
theory of change, and then we say, how do we want to give them,
you know, the possibility to edit their theory of change,
or we say maybe the carbon emissions thing is the most important thing,
how can we, you know, allow them to edit their,
uh, their, uhm,
carbon emissions data, and we can maybe,
you know, for the theory of a change, we can maybe reuse some of
the old code, uh, but basically,
I think the old code is rather going to phase out,
uhm,
and we just, uh, you know, add this function on top of our,
uh, new data and new URL-extracted,
uh, code.
Okay, then we have this. MyPortfolios.
This is actually extremely
helpful, and basically, the way it currently works is that it asks me to
create a new portfolio, and then it even has, like, an AI integration that
was, like, one of the last tools that we built, where basically I can
say,
you know, that's my website, if I do have a website for the portfolio,
uhm,
and then it fills in,
like, the data for the portfolio,
but actually it doesn't work. I think it's broken,
but I think the code should be there. But the one
thing that works really well is the option to create
new portfolios. And then see, it's not beautiful,
we can maybe, you know, improve a little bit the design,
but basically, I know that Vista already asked,
can we, you know, build, can we have several projects,
and I told them, I think what you label project is like a sub-portfolio,
and basically, you know, we have extracted all our companies,
and then, uhm, you know,
we need to make sure that we, uhm,
manage access rights to the different companies,
but basically, uhm,
you know, Vista, uhm,
employee can then add any Vista internal portfolio company to
a new portfolio, and I'm doing this already, for example,
here, I've built, you know, this House of Games,
I just added, uhm, two, uhm,
two companies, and then, you know, that's the House of Games portfolio,
and then maybe the House of Games manager, he would only add his company,
so this thing is pretty cool, and whether we want to show it to
all portfolio companies or just to the portfolio managers,
we can decide, but the functionality is pretty cool.
The, the, the downside is that,
you know, once I click on the portfolio company,
I get to the old app, and we don't need it anymore,
we would, uhm, go directly to,
you know, the old app to this, uh,
screen here. Okay.
So, the, the downside is a little bit that, uh,
what do we do if, you know, I think there are a lot of
use cases now. Initially, we thought, thought portfolio managers are like,
uh, Vista or,
uh, HWC, they would typically have a webpage,
and then we built this, uh,
uhm, let's go back to my portfolios. You know, in order to create a
portfolio, uhm, you have this, uh, little, uh, uhm, how do you call it,
step-by-step, uh, thing where you add,
yeah, exactly, and you,
obviously, you can see, you
can also edit the portfolio, uh,
or delete it, and, uhm, Mmm.
And when you click on it, then you'd, you know, get to that actual
portfolio, and now, House of Games,
for example, they, I, they do actually have a webpage,
but in some cases, you know, maybe, uh,
Ravat would just say, oh, let's create, like,
uh, new companies,
uh, uhm, portfolio,
and then there's no URL for this,
so, you know,
ideally, we would say, uh,
like, uh, when, when we create it,
we would maybe say, does it have a webpage? If yes,
it would maybe fill in this data, and,
uh, if not, then we would probably just collect,
we'd just give it a portfolio name, and that's it. But in the,
in the first step,
I can just tell them, you know, if you create a new portfolio and
you don't have a webpage, then you can just give it,
like, a portfolio name, and click on save and exit.
So, uh, you know, we could keep it this way,
uh, that, you know, at least it allows them to create a portfolio,
even though it's maybe too complex, uhm,
and in a second step, we could maybe, you know, have this model where
we ask them, is it, uhm,
uhm, one with,
uh, you know, specific com-, uh,
data, or is it just the name and you don't need anything behind it?
Hmm, okay. So,
instead of, like, extracting, uhm,
it would be, we would have, like, a wizard like this,
you're saying? Well, I don't think,
well, the wizard is there in any case, but I think the difference would
be that we just need a portfolio name, that's it.
Okay. If they, it's, you know, if it's new companies within Vista,
and Vista creates, you know, that creates three sub-portfolios.
One is new companies, one is, like, FinTech,
and one is another one, or just,
you know, maybe projective new clients,
and he wants to add new clients to, to the database.
Uhm, he won't need,
you know, portfolio,
there's no company name for that portfolio, it would be Vista.
Portfolio formation date, well, it's, it's, there's,
I mean, yeah, when he, when he created it, maybe he could call it,
uhm, type of legal entity,
well, there's non, legal form, non-internet presence,
there wouldn't be anything, location, you know,
there's a lot of, the, the reason why we collected this data is that
we also created this, uhm,
uhm, once you click on a portfolio,
we also created this, uh,
public profile, and that's where you, you use the data for,
you know, the size, uh, and so on,
and, uhm,
that's, that's where we have this, why we have this data collection for,
and then we, you know, we added the ventures to that portfolio,
uhm,
but I don't think we currently need public profiles for these portfolios.
Okay. So,
you could also. Say, make it simpler.
And when you click on new portfolio, just give it a portfolio name.
That's it. Yeah. That makes sense.
And then, yeah. And then like later, you know,
if they actually want a public profile, then they can do that,
but then there's like a separate pool for that. Right. And then that way
you can just, that's better. I like that.
Yeah. You can opt in public profile if you need it.
Yeah. Yeah. So that's simple.
So basically for the public profile,
you can use this, uh,
this screen. Um,
ah, yeah. Okay. If there's only a name, would be maybe,
it's quite nice to have these tiles because basically suppose you have the three
or five portfolios and if you only have the portfolio name,
well, there's, there's not in all cases a,
uh, picture. So maybe we'd need to take away the,
or no, not logo. What do you think?
Do you have an idea of how we should display, you know,
is it the list of portfolios then, which should just be a list view
or a tile view or, uh.
Um. Cause that's based on,
you know, how AI generated, uh,
ideally, you know, if you better the URL.
In the portfolio generation tool,
then, you know, it's, it takes the data from there.
Yeah. Yeah. I can play around with it.
Um,
it might make, it might make sense to have it just be like a
list view. Um, no image or like description.
Um, so yeah.
Um, uh,
yeah, but I can play around with it. Yeah. This is great.
I like it. Not a huge challenge.
So, we have my profile, we have book mentor session,
we have my portfolios, we have my
ventures. We said we don't need it.
What we would need is the screen here.
Let me just go back. Oops.
Manage public profile of a venture.
Where would we add this? Would that be just
a, Uhm, I mean, that could probably be on the profile,
like, the three dots maybe,
like in a list.
Or we could just, you know, call it, uh,
Edit my venture, for example. But then,
Edit public profile.
So basically, there are two different use cases. How would,
like, a, A portfolio company that only has one,
You know, they only want to edit their own, uhm,
company public profile. How would they access it?
And we could also imagine that,
uh, a portfolio manager currently has,
like, this list of, uhm,
You know, there could also be, I think they do not have access to
the public profile if you, uh,
if you add it to the EditView.
Is there also the public profile?
I think we added this, the link to the public profile phone,
uhm, Uhm,
I think it's, The public profile link,
I think, is, Default?
It's in the, Well, no, it's on the modal,
right? I don't think, Did we add it to the table?
Yes, we did. Yeah,
I asked you, yeah, because it was too complicated to... Okay,
if I Ah, yeah,
if I just, Isn't there a better way to go back to,
Edit, View, Reset to Default.
Done. So here we see now the public profile.
Yeah, there you go. And then basically,
so the Portfolio Manager would, ,see
the public profile, ,or
edit the public profile. Yeah,
you know, we need the functionality to get to this screen here,
where basically Manage Public Profile.
And we could say, well, it's just the company that has the ability to
do it. And then we could just add to this drop-down or
to the menu item on the left, you know,
Edit Public Profile. Thank you.
However, if you have access to several portfolio companies,
then the question is, you know, would you see a list of,
uh, portfolio companies similar to what we already have,
uhm,
here? and then you know either you would need to get view
public profile or I
think we could also say then edit public profile basically and,
you know, if you get here, if you click on view,
uh, here, you would actually get to this screen here,
manage public profile. We could re-re-label it also,
uh,
here, you know,
manage public profile And then I believe once we have the public
profile management, there's a way to preview how it looks like.
Isn't there a way to preview? We'll just preview exactly.
So basically, we could say, uh,
you know, at some point in time, uhm,
the public profiles will be public anyways.
So the most important part is, you know, edit the public profile and if
you want to see it, then you need to click on the preview.
You know what I mean? Or is that what I do? I can't lose
you. I think, I think so.
So, yeah. Well,
yeah, I mean, yeah, maybe you can walk through it one more time, actually.
Yeah. So as a portfolio
company, so let's say as,
uh,
they, sorry, uh, uh, let's go to our Vista portfolio.
I like that better. Uhm,
my portfolios, let's go to Vista.
So, Compute database database
So,
assume you are, uh,
Cantaloupe GmbH, uh, manager,
and then you create your account, and then obviously you would not
see the whole list of all other organizations,
you would only see Cantaloupe,
and then basically in the old app,
you would need to get somehow to this screen
My Ventures, and then Manage Public Profile.
So how do I get to this screen? And we could either say,
well, uh, Cantaloupe GmbH When they click on
their, uhm,
on their drop-down here, they will see my profile,
they'll be able to edit their profile, they'll see Book a Mentor Session,
they'll see my portfolios,
most likely, that, uh, you know, would be empty.
And when they click on My Ventures, it could simply be called Edit Venture.
And then obviously the can edit their venture. Or edit public
profile. So this is for, I guess I'm a little,
For a portfolio company. Okay,
so yeah, so this is like a different view for if it's a portfolio
company versus, versus if it's someone managing portfolios.
Exactly, exactly. Uhm,
and I was just wondering, You know how How do we give a portfolio
company access to, you know,
manage my public profile? And how would you give a portfolio manager
access to edit a public company profile?
And I believe it would be acceptable that a portfolio
manager can edit a,
uhm, public profile. public company profile.
So let's just assume there's a company who says,
oh, I don't have the time, portfolio company to manage it,
but I give you the okay to, uh, you know,
change the number of employees to, uh,
from 10 to 20, then it would be good that the portfolio manager
who sees this list here could also get access to this
screen here manage public profile of this certain company.
And you could either give them access by clicking on here.
And instead of viewing directly, the public profile,
you could simply relabel this, um,
or just add a new column. You know, one is public profile and one
is edit public profile. I'm not sure whether we need both columns.
And when you click on edit, then obviously you would get to,
um,
to this screen first or directly
to this one here where you can edit your public profile.
And how can a portfolio manager get access to this screen
for a list of portfolio companies?
Does that make sense? Yeah, it does make sense. I think these are like
two different, yeah, piece, like UIs to think through,
to be honest. So, okay. Like,
I'm, I mean, I think like
one of the way you can imagine it as well is,
um, for a portfolio manager,
maybe there's that table with the companies.
Yes. And then there's the link. I mean,
we can, of course, add a link for like view.
And then on the view, there's like a three dots for like edit or
something. Yeah. Um,
or you could just add like an edit link as well on the table.
Um, or you can add like a separate UI to the left that is
just to look at portfolio companies and their public profiles.
Um, for example, um,
uh, for portfolio companies themselves,
yeah, maybe they have a dropdown, kind of like you said earlier,
that just says like edit the public profile or something,
or like view public profile, and then they can edit it from right on
the page. Um,
but, yeah, I think those are probably two different UI experiences.
Um,
but it does make sense now, like, um,
like I'm, I'm, yeah, like how,
how the dropdowns might need to change based on like what they can see.
Okay. Sounds good. We can also,
you know, have a back and forth, uh, in the next, uh,
the coming time. Uh, but that's basically the functionality that we will need.
By the way, would you want to record the meeting so you can listen
to it again? Or, uh, I don't think I clicked on, uh,
um, on, uh,
transcribing or, you know, if you,
if you take notes and that's sufficient for you, that's, that's fine for me.
Um, probably easier.
Yeah. I mean, we can definitely record it. I think like,
I get like,
for me, this, this, like, this is a great discussion and I'm glad that
we're having it. I can get the context and,
um, uh,
but also as well, like, for me, it's going to be the most helpful
if, um, like I can take notes,
but also just kind of getting your direction in terms of like written
down, like, like what's the highest priority here to start with?
Like, what do you want to see first?
And, um, uh,
what else? Uh, and also like, if you could take kind of like how
you've been doing, uh, before,
it's really good. Like if you can even just take a screenshot and like
write notes on the screenshot or put, do the screenshot and then point to
like another screenshot, you know, like connect,
like, even if you could take like an hour to do that,
that saves a lot of time. Like, trust me.
Great. Um, so I'm happy to do it. Yeah.
So I think, I think the session is great. And I mean,
I, to be honest with you, I mean, I, I even have more time,
like I have, we can keep chatting for another 30 minutes as well.
Um, but then, yeah, once, once we're done,
once we're, we're, we're closing this out,
then just kind of like a final readout of,
hey, like, okay, this is like,
you know, what to work on, et cetera. And then as well,
I can go back and look at the code and just explain to you
like what it will take just so you know, you're on the same page
about the time and stuff. And like, we're aligned that way.
And, or else you might say, oh, actually let's reorder these because that's going
to take longer than I thought, et cetera. And then I can like just
execute against that, like list. Um,
but yeah, but I think, yeah, I think, but I think this is,
to me, what I'm gathering here is, is that,
like a couple, like big things, right?
Um, we want to be able to really start to show this kind of
white label concept. Um,
we can start with Vista and make sure that,
um, the login screens kind of have,
like present that vision, right,
with the designs. And then we can have it,
the login go right into the newer one. Um,
and then on the side, we'll,
we can bring in the old app options for the most part,
with the exception of, like, my ventures,
um, for, like, portfolio managers. Um,
and then, so maybe we, maybe we do that first,
and then once we have that, and then I can, like, go back and
make additional edits for the venture-only perspective,
right? Because then the menu might change. Um,
and as well, um,
we'll want to hook in the public profiles that we made before with Vista
Designs into this new app. And,
um, yeah, and then we can kind of go from there.
So I think, like, that, you know, that kind of drive,
that vision is really starting to become a lot bigger to me.
Right. In this call. And for me now, yeah,
and for me, you know, talking about, talking to you now,
it, it, you know, it's, it gets clearer for me how to do the
different steps and I can then, you know,
make a short PowerPoint with, you know,
screenshots and, uh, and, uh,
how I believe it might look like and,
uh, priorities, uh, because I wasn't able to do it before the call.
Yeah, yeah, definitely. And we'll, yeah, I mean, this is,
it's great to, sometimes it's great to just kind of,
yeah, to kind of, like, work it, like workshop it and then,
you know, get some feedback. So yeah, that's, I mean, that's exactly what's important.
Uh, the other thing I'll call out. have one more item.
Oh, sorry. Yeah.
One more thing I just wanted to call out.
go ahead. Yeah. Is, um, I believe, like, so right now we have app.impact.io
and that's on one DigitalOcean,
like, VM. And then we have, like map.impactforum.
website.io and that's on another DigitalOcean VM.
It's likely if we have the,
the vista.impact.io, we'll have to have a,
an additional, um, virtual machine.
Um, it, it, I just want to call that out because that might increase
your, your monthly costs. Hopefully it won't increase it by that much.
Hopefully it'll only increase it by like a couple bucks,
but, um, we might, we might need to do that.
So I just want to give a heads up. It might even be,
uh, does that mean it's stored on a different
server? Like a different account? It's like a separate,
uh,
like a separate, uh, uh,
bucket? Um,
I think it can be in the same account. It's just a new machine.
And, and let me double check this too, because maybe there's a way where
we don't need to do that. But, but there,
but it might, we might need to have a different,
uh, an additional, what's called like virtual machine,
but it would be in the same account. Okay.
Yeah. Spontaneously it sounds like additional,
you know, virtual machine, whatever that is.
It sounds, it sounds good, uh, to have it separate somehow. So, so I
can tell them, you know, this is your white label solution.
Your data is separate in a separate bucket and it won't get a,
sorry, it won't get messed up with other data.
So it's high security level. So I'm happy to pay the couple of bucks
extra. Correct. Uh, although I don't know what a virtual machine is.
Well, I mean, every, all of the benefits that you said are correct.
So, you know, at least you know that part.
Yeah. It, that's a let's go for the additional virtual machine rather than,
uh, mixing it up and then they get,
you know, worried about, uh, the whole,
uh, data security and so on.
Okay, cool. All right, cool.
So, um, yeah, that sounds great. I'll,
uh, I'll let you know when that needs to happen and stuff.
Um, but yeah, just like I said,
I just want to give you a, the, the heads up about it.
Okay. Sounds good. Then,
uh, the final thing that we haven't discussed yet that is somewhat
relevant and I love to use it and it's fully functional is this manage
team function where you click manage your team and
then i can give any
person access to you know, using the old app I can give,
uh, uh, individuals access and I actually use it only for portfolios companies as
soon as it gives someone access to a portfolio in the new app they
can then click, you know, on this,
uh,
uh, uhm, link that leads them to the new app and then you have
only companies that have been added to that new app so basically there's some
link already between the old and the new as I can create the portfolio
in the old app and then, you know, that's mirrored in the new app.
And, uhm,
then giving individuals access to a portfolio is
what I currently use so basically if I want to give,
uh, uh, for example, we had,
uh, let me just go, uh,
Ukraina Data Datenbank Vista.
I wanted to have, like, a list of 20 Ukraine companies so I just
created, you know, in the old app this Ukraine,
uh, portfolio. And then,
obviously, I clicked on this link to the URL extractor that leads us to
the new app. I added companies to that portfolio and then I went
to team management. I click on provide access to a portfolio
and then I gave, uh,
uhm, Helge access and after that he was invited and he was able to,
uh, access that portfolio.
So this thing is pretty far powerful and,
uhm, the same was true for ventures.
Now here it becomes a little bit more complicated as,
uh, at some point in time and we'll have like this type of,
Uh, when portfolio companies will have,
uhm,
maybe some companies that I add or someone adds as prospective client
companies but from Vista and then we might have,
like, other clients that we have and,
uhm,
well, actually it does work the same because,
basically, once you get access to a portfolio,
you're being invited to the portfolio,
you would see a list of all ventures in that portfolio.
And once I'm adding new companies and I
say I want to share a venture with someone else,
much. I was able to also share a venture.
Maybe that functionality is not needed initially.
We simply say the only thing you can share is portfolios.
Do we need to share ventures? What use case could there
be? As everyone can add their own
venture. Do you think it's easier to
just copy the whole bunch of code and then,
you know, have this, uh, venture access and portfolio access and
implement it all at once?
Or do you say, well, let's just delete the whole venture thing and just
allow someone to give access to a portfolio and then obviously
the person that has been invited to a portfolio has access to all companies
in that portfolio? Um,
I mean, off the top of my head,
that second option likely seems like
less complex, like, easier, faster to implement,
but, you know, like I said,
I might have to look at the code. Like, it could, like,
maybe, maybe not. Maybe we get number one for free, um,
or something, but, uh,
but yeah, probably, probably the step-by-step version and,
and until I can verify what, how much time it would take to do
the entire thing.
So let's just assume we use this model here to,
uh, give someone access to a portfolio and then obviously once I've,
uh, you know, invited them, I can see,
uh,
sort by name,
filter by all the
companies. Ideally it would be able to filter by companies
or portfolios. Do I have a portfolio here at Vista?
I can see basically who has
access to the portfolio. Uhm,
but then, uhm,
sorry, can I be back in one minute?
Yeah, yeah. Okay, just a second.
Yeah.
Hey, I'm back.
I just have a little
bit of a cold,
so I just wanted to
blow my nose,
but I'm back.
Uhm.
So this thing is,
yeah, yeah, yeah, all good,
uhm, this thing is actually more complex than I thought because,
uh, you know, the question is what do they get access to,
because there's also the use case that I am now the manager of,
uhm, of, uh,
let's say the company, uh, uhm, Cantaloupe,
and then I say, oh, I have my fellow,
uhm,
colleagues, because I'm leaving the company or because just two people want to,
you know, edit the Cantaloupe profile,
and then I should be able to give them access
to not the portfolio.
but actually the company,
but basically you would then invite them to
the same account that a portfolio
company has, you know, we discussed how would the menu items look like for
a portfolio company. And,
uh, basically there should be the option to invite them and then
they would see, you know,
the, the, the company, they would have the option to edit the
public profile and they could
create a portfolio and once they added portfolio companies,
they could I
think I need to think through it. I need
to think through it, how that needs to work.
But that's important, because, uh,
that's also part of what we sold to Vista, that, uh, basically you have,
uh, you know, the accounts.
Account management and team management option implemented,
where, uh, a, uh,
portfolio company can invite other collaborators
to manage their portfolio company. Yeah.
And once, uh, we give them access also to,
you know, impact tools about their company,
Thank you. Um,
they, you know, they should jointly be able to manage then maybe the fear
of change or so, whatever we want to give them access to.
Yeah. Um,
I'll think through it based on our call now.
Yeah. Yeah. I,
so think through it.
And then also, um,
I'll, uh,
like I'll, I'll send over some bullet points that I gathered from the call.
And then if there's, uh,
you think through it and if there's still any open questions about it,
um, one thing you can do is you can also just let me know
what is still an open question. Yes.
And then I can, you know,
and what's me, just let me know like open questions and then also let
me know the things that we need or,
you know, that whole thing, like the list.
Um, you know, as, as well as any images and stuff like that.
And then I can, for the thing that you're really not,
or you want like some feedback on, like I can take what we need
and then the open questions. And then I can say,
you know, I can kind of give you some options and like,
yeah. I'll be like, what that might look like. Sounds good.
Sounds good. That's like another, that's another way we can do some of that.
Uh, some of that, um, that stuff that's not resolved.
Yeah. So that's very helpful. Um,
let's, let's proceed this way and maybe leave this discussion here for the moment,
do you have another five minutes to just evaluate,
uh, or we can ask reconnect if you have time for the rest of
the week to have, uh, maybe it's better next time to set up another
meeting, but you can choose whatever's best for you. Okay.
Maybe we should have one discussion prior to meeting,
um,
Christian, uh, who, for,
you know, who requested this tool like a lead generation.
I think we should maybe discuss a little bit how that could look like,
what options there are, initial ideas,
um, how that could be implemented that will make the discussion more efficient.
Sure. Should we set up a separate, um,
meeting, or do you want to discuss now five minutes?
Both is fine for me, I don't have a preference. Well,
I mean, I, I have, like,
20 minutes that I can even chat about that right now.
Then let's chat, continue chatting for another five minutes.
Yeah, yeah, we can, we can just chat about it now,
um. Yeah. Get the juices in.
So, yeah, yeah. So,
I think what he, the use case is, The use case that he described
to me is that, you know,
he would love to have an agent where he gives a sample company that
he would like to reach out to as a prospective tenant to his house
of games. You tell him that's the ideal company,
and then, you know, add some criteria in terms of,
uh, size, in terms of, uh, growth indicators,
uhm,
And, uh, then have this agent, you know, go and collect a list of
companies based on these specif- the specifications.
Mhm. I don't think he necessarily needs the whole integration
with, you know, it reaches automatically out,
sends emails, uh,
responds to emails, follow-up emails.
But, you know, that would be nice to have. But also,
Ravad was a little bit, uh,
on the one hand, you know, the Vista CEO,
uhm, said,
uh, you know, we need more, more non,
uh, impact use cases and I need to fill up my spaces and I
have, you know, difficulties. And if, you know, if you can fill up my
space, uhm,
you know, that, that's worth a lot more than your subscription,
basically. So he said that's for him,
like, where he has pressure. Uhm,
at the same time, Ravad said, you know, don't,
you know, before you've not implemented our current products,
you know, don't start selling a new product that basically you have 20 open
ends but nothing is fully implemented. So he said,
for him, it's also fine to have, you know, some, uh,
basic MVP that sort of helps solving this problem.
It doesn't allow us to sell our products to,
you know, the board and it doesn't need,
like, you know, the super duper thing.
Yeah. So, uh, I don't think it necessarily needs to send out emails and
everything. I think what would be interesting for him, just see the leads of
these companies and maybe here there could be a link back to our existing
tool. Maybe we could actually,
you know, once we've identified the URLs, we could almost create,
um, these,
uh,
uhm, company profiles for these companies and maybe we would add some criteria,
but basically, you know, we have news, we have growth,
we have all of this stuff. So basically,
uh, uhm, you know, could we first identify just
the URL of potential companies and then add them to our database and that's
maybe it. Maybe adapt the database a little bit more to,
to, you know, leave away the sustainability criteria for these companies and,
uhm, you know, uh,
so, you know, add maybe a few data points.
That could be one solution. I,
uh, you know, given the whole,
uhm, uhm,
tracking today on LinkedIn, I saw a
post pop up for a company that is called, let me just go to
it, I sent me an email with The name is here.
Instantly, Instantly
AI.
Uh, find clients instantly and basically they have
the sales agent that,
uhm,
leads database and what they have,
what I understand is, they,
you know, have an existing database of companies that,
that they then give their clients access to.
I think they say, is it 4 million or whatever, let me just check
what they say. 450 million leads,
uh, with AI. Uhm,
and so the question is, if he's,
he, he's interested in, uh,
you know, companies in the games industry,
do we need to connect to an existing database,
do we, like, Crunchbase, but then the question is,
maybe some of the companies he's looking for,
they're not in on Crunchbase, as he said, he also needs some,
you know, creative people, and then he said,
he used, he did use a tool previously that was searched through LinkedIn
profiles, but he wasn't very happy with it, uhm,
so I think the core question is, do we need to have a database
ourselves, or is there a way to just identify URLs and then
build our database gradually.
I don't know, my assumption is the best would be,
you know, have a database and then have our AI search that database,
uhm, but that's probably linked with significant costs,
I assume, you know, I don't think LinkedIn would give us access
to their, to their, you know, uhm, we need to check, uhm, but that's
a core question that I have, how could we implement such a tool.
Yeah, yeah, I mean, it's a,
it's a, it's a great question, I think that,
so, off the top of my head, I'll tell you,
yeah, like, I'll just confirm, like, generally how tools like this are done,
or can be done, uhm, but then,
then maybe we can think about how we might do it for,
for this, like, like, MVP version,
but, uh, but yeah, so, like, Instantly has been around for
several years, actually, uhm,
I'm not sure how long, but they've definitely been around for several years,
and I'm sure they've been scraping the internet for,
like, years, and so, yeah,
they have, like, 450 million different leads that they've probably
collected from LinkedIn,
Twitter, they probably have been like looking at,
Google search data, uhm,
they might be looking at Facebook marketing data,
uhm, like, they probably just use,
like, a lot of different sources and tools,
uhm, to try to get some insight,
uh, they might, they might be connected to several,
like, news aggregators, uhm,
but, yeah, they, I'm sure that, by now, they've probably connected to thousands,
if not more, of sources on the internet, and, uhm, and,
like, scrape them to build this database,
and then what happens is, when you talk to their AI,
or when you search their, this,
this database, like, you're just searching, like, you're just searching a DB they already
have, right, it's not like they're searching live, like,
even the AI is just, like, using, uh,
uh, queries to, like, query the data that they already have,
like, the AI is not, like, live scraping the internet,
even if they might say that, so,
that's how an app like this works,
uhm, I think,
uh,
an MVP, so,
okay, so then for our app, like, we,
we would probably have to do it similarly, unless we had some other way
to have the AI agent, like,
do it live, which is possible, like, you can tell the AI agent,
try to look at these different websites,
uhm, but you just have to be careful, because,
like, uh, a lot of websites have bot protection,
right, like, even when we tried scraping before,
scraping social media was, like, was just difficult,
because, uh, they have these, like, bot protections.
So, I would say, for an MVP,
like, for this, uhm,
we might wanna just see,
like, like, I, like, I might wanna, like, just see what I could find
on, like, offline, to, like, populate, uh,
a mini database, just in case, uhm,
with a certain amount of companies, and then we can have the AI also
try to find its own companies, but then have,
have, like, a fallback of, uhm,
maybe some companies that we've, like, found, like, offline that could fit his query
or something, uhm, but,
yeah, I think, like, the, you know, a,
a, a, as we're seeing right now, like, his idea,
like, on its own is, like,
it, it could be its own company, haha, uhm,
you know what I mean, and so, uh,
we can definitely implement it, but I think how we implement it would be
definitely on, like, uhm, a smaller scale at first,
uhm, to just kind of prove the concept,
uh, unless you want to go for something bigger, we can definitely do that,
but of course that takes time. No.
I mean, it would be great in the medium term, but,
But, uh, you know, I think it's better to be,
eh, eh, best in class in, you know, what we do, rather than, uh,
third in class in everything what we do,
haha. Yeah,
and I think here it would be, you know,
obviously it should create value, and then when you reach out to other science
parks and realize, oh, they love to have this integrated into their tools,
like a complete portfolio management, and maybe,
you know, we have some future use cases where we have impact investors
who want to, you know, or systemic impact investors,
uhm, then, you know,
maybe that tool would become more sophisticated,
but based on the request from Ravad,
so the project manager, uhm,
it's more like a, uh, you know,
maybe we can help them, help this,
uh, Christian a little bit with what he does without,
uh, you know, spending, uh, millions on,
on the whole, uhm, so,
you know, is there a way how we can, you know, test this thing
without spending a lot of too much, uh,
money and resources, uhm, and I think that's the sweet spot that we need
to find with him, asking him, maybe he tells us exactly what our needs
are, companies, typically they're not in CrunchBase,
you know, they're very small, or maybe he says,
you know, geographic regions is only Europe or worldwide,
and maybe based on this, you know, we can limit down the companies and
maybe do a specific search for these companies and then initially we'd say,
well, we only need the game sector,
we only need, uh, you know, what databases could we,
could we access. Yeah. Yeah.
I, I yeah. And then maybe that, that could,
could, uh, could be a starting point. Yeah.
If you, uh, and maybe, you know, we can discuss this on,
on, uh, Tuesday, but for example,
for example, right. If he,
if he actually already has a process where he likes,
where he, he can find these companies, like if,
um, if he's told, if he's told you this before,
or if he has an A, B, C, D, E, you know,
and he says, oh yeah, I have like my assistant,
uh, instead of LinkedIn, I have them go to Twitter or like,
instead of, you know, LinkedIn, I,
I like them to look at these gaming,
um, news publications,
right. That's because then, because then that's how I get the best about the
upcoming gamers. Like, so if he already has a process for this,
then we can very likely automate that process and then,
have an AI agent do it, that would probably be the most efficient way
to get this done. Um,
but if he doesn't have a process for this, then like, that's fine.
We can obviously create one ourselves too.
Um, but, uh, but yeah,
so it's like, yeah,
if we, if we don't want to spend a bunch of time and money
on this and create like our own database and like have this whole scraping
engine, then probably the quickest way to value.
Who would just be to figure out where does he get the,
where does he find the companies that he likes?
And then like go there, you know,
that sounds good. Um, okay.
I think that's maybe almost sufficient. I'll think about it too.
And, uh, by the way, I, I checked it.
He said, you know, he used this thing that accessed LinkedIn profiles and he
wasn't very happy with it. I'm not sure whether he has heard of Instantly,
but it sounds like the tool that, uh, you know, could be very useful
for him. So, uh,
there's always the question, you know, um,
and they don't seem to be too expensive, uh,
looking at their pricing. So, um,
I mean, another, I mean, I don't know if,
I don't know if you're open to this, but, um,
I'm just going to toss out the idea, you know, but Instantly does sound
expensive pricing, right? And it's like, we could,
uh, uh, we could likely use Instantly,
you know, and, uh, uh,
at first and see if he likes it or if he's willing to pay
or something. And then if he does, then kind of go from there.
That's like kind of another like cheat, cheat, cheat of doing that.
Um, well, there could be a cheat, cheat,
cheat, or it could So that's the official thing where we say,
you know, you don't want to use 15 different apps.
And, uh, we,
uh, you know, we give you access to this,
to have a trial and, uh, it's part of our services.
Uh, although my assumption is,
uh, I'm not sure, you know, probably instantly would make this rather expensive.
So I, but I, I'm, I'm open unless,
you know, we say we just get an account for us and then integrate
into our app. And you think they won't discover it. Um,
I'm, you know, whether it's an official request or an unofficial request or whether
we tell him where the data comes from or not,
I'm open for, uh, for different, um,
solutions. Yeah, absolutely.
Well, yeah, I mean that, I mean that, you know,
there you go. That's, that's yet another solution we can explore.
I think that, uh, it instantly has an API.
Bye. So I can, like, look at that to see if there's a programmatic
way that we can, you know, look and,
you know, I'll just do it really quick, but I'll see if there's a
programmatic way that we can use instantly data,
um, or, you know, if, if we might have to scrape it,
um, and then, yeah, you can kind of think about,
uh, and, you know, we can use that maybe to put together a possible
MVP. And in general, you can just think about,
uh, yeah, if we get an account for,
you know, Impact Foresight, and then is this a feature that you can provide
to multiple clients and make money off of, right?
Because, uh, because that's fine, right? Especially if we're,
um, I imagine they have an API because of this exact reason.
And so it's just a matter of, like, you know, are you able to
make more money from it from the downstream customers than what you're paying for
your cost? But yeah,
you know, even that is just another option. Yeah.
And we could, you know, just use, uh,
use it to identify potential companies and then,
you know, create maybe profiles and add some value to it by,
you know, looking at potential needs,
by looking, I'm not sure whether, uh,
uh, Instantly has access to their news streams or whatsoever.
So you can, you could just download this potential client database and then,
uh, our news streams also takes a little while.
And, uh, then, you know, over time,
over the two or three months, he will then get news from his,
uh, potential client database. And then he can reach out to those where he
see, oh, growth event and so on. Um,
that could be an interesting solution, actually. Yeah.
Yeah. So, yeah. I could even say,
you know, we, we just, you know, access, uhm,
Later. Instantly. Once we download all the companies
that, uh,
uhm, he's potentially interested in, we add them to our database and then he
can see the ones that perform well,
that have growth events, get news about them.
Okay. Let me think about it. Maybe I need one check-in,
uh, to make sure how we can communicate about him.
You know, do we say openly about instantly or not?
Uh, but we can also do that via Slack, but,
uh, you know, as an idea generation, I think that was very helpful.
Yeah, absolutely. Absolutely. And, uh,
yeah, I mean, I think maybe in this, in this upcoming call,
we can kind of just ask him about the need and stuff.
And, uh, and then in a later call we can,
or, or in a follow-up, in a follow-up,
yeah. Once we've had the time to think this through,
we can talk about, like, what the solution might be,
but yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. The,
the slight, slight, uh, pressure that we have is that,
uh, the, um,
meeting with Vista then is on Thursday with the Vista CEO.
And ideally I could, you know, give him,
you know, some suggestion where I say, you know, we can integrate a solution
without, you know, adding additional budget, or we say,
oh, we can add something, but it will, it will cost a hundred K
more. Uh, so, you know, having some,
uh, Thank you. Uh, very high level,
um, um,
suggestions there might be helpful,
but we'll see what's possible.
You know, as I said, Rawat said he doesn't want to have too much
complexity. He prefers to have his tool implemented and then,
you know, add new features. And I need to find out whether,
you know, um, yeah,
I believe, you know, I think the CEO, he does have something in pressure
to fill up his, uh, his, uh, Science Park.
And, uh, that's changed. It was in the same way one or two years
ago. Yeah. And, uh, this,
uh, House of Games, and there's another one, Phubic,
they're like, uh, politically, you know, there's like the,
the federal government and the local government involved.
And there were some, I think also critical news about,
uh, you know, slow pickup, uh,
tenant pickup. So I think he does have pressure. So,
yeah. So that's maybe why he, you know, uh,
adds this now, but, uh,
you know, I'm not sure how much he wants to add this feature
just to sell his board better,
the sustainability tool where sustainability maybe don't matter,
doesn't matter so much anymore for the, for the board or whether he really
wants to have a two, it's maybe a mix of both. Yeah.
Yeah. Okay. Yeah. I think, um,
yeah, I, I think like a couple of things.
One, if we can get, uh,
specifically, specifically for the gaming,
um, if we can really get for,
yeah, if we can get really clear on like specifically what they're looking for
or what they like, because he said that he used LinkedIn,
but he didn't, he didn't see anything he liked.
So then we can ask, so what do you like? Like,
what are the types of things that you like? And as much as we
can get information on that, then that will make us finding potential companies easier.
You know, we can maybe even use instantly to find an app filters based
on what he says, and then be able to kind of say,
okay, yeah, here's, here's at least something you can initially play with.
Um, and then,
similar for the CEO as well, um,
in terms of like filling up the science section parks, I,
I might lean in on saying, you know,
what specifically are you interested in looking for?
You know, what, what kind of companies would you like to fill it up
and see what he says? And then we can kind of come back and
say, okay, well, we know how to,
like, you know, I can go and see how we can find that or
whatever, but yeah, then we can kind of come back and say,
okay, this is how we're going to do that. Right.
This is how we're going to meet what you're looking for. Um,
so that's, that's, that might be, uh,
something to go for. Yeah. Sounds good.
Uh, but overall, you know, with this limitation that,
you know, they want to pivot a little bit, uh, they're still fully on
board. They, uh, although the contract is not signed,
they've agreed on the 65 K and they want to reach out to other
science parks. And, uh,
so they're fully committed, fully on board. And, uh,
this client sort of, uh, you know, everything goes smoothly.
I would still say it's movie and,
uh, now I need to reach out to some other older clients and potential
new clients, but, uh, you know, things are still, um,
looking good. Okay. Okay,
cool. Well, Hey, I mean, you know, it's, uh,
what, what, what's been happening in the last, you know,
month or so is like, uh, I think shock to the world,
but, um, but yeah, I mean, you know, that's kind of part of life
and, uh, yeah, we just, you know,
roll with the punches and I, it sounds like all things considered,
things are still trending positively. So yes,
that's great. So at this point,
yes. Awesome. Awesome.
Great. Thank you for your time. As I said,
I was very happy with, uh, what you produced over the past,
uh, months, um,
and, uh, we'll. Maybe I have a few more frequent check-ins until you're,
uh, you're, um,
away and, um,
so we can, you know, manage priorities, make sure what's,
what's coming next and, uh, that I'm pretty sure that,
uh, everything looks good. Awesome. Okay.
That sounds really great. Thanks so much, Ingo. Thank you.
Have a wonderful rest of your day. You as well.
Thank you. Bye.